

I'm a freelance visual/UX designer and sometimes front-end developer trying to figure out what's next for me. I am interested in making products that improve people's lives and make them smile. I believe in living what you love, and that includes my work. I would love to get my creative juices flowing and collaboratively work with a design team focusing on great experiences.

- ANGELLOV.ES
- **₩** @ANGELK
- ANGEL.KITTIYACHAVALIT@GMAIL.COM

#### **SKILLS**

Visual design, UI/UX design, Adobe Suite, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, rock climbing, photography, making greeting cards, laughing, and making name tags.

#### **EDUCATION**

**University of California, Berkeley** B.A., Economics *August 2008* 

## **AWARDS**

**GSMA mWomen Design Challenge Grand Prize Winner** 

February 2013

# References available upon request

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Freelance Designer**

Design & Happiness Studio, San Francisco, CA October 2009–Present

I do graphic design, web and mobile design, UX/UI design, and front-end development for various clients.

### **Designer in Residence**

Code for America, San Francisco, CA *December 2012–December 2013* 

I designed marketing material for all of the 5 programs of Code for America as well as mentored fellows with their projects.

#### 2012 Fellow

Code for America, San Francisco, CA *January 2012–November 2012* 

I worked for the city of Chicago, where I was in charge of designing and performing the user testing of web applications that dealt with 311 data. I also helped with front-end development. In addition to Chicago, I also helped design Honolulu Answers and other material for Code for America as a whole that included a newsletter template, the initial site for their Accelerator program, and an icon known as the flag tag.

# **User Experience Designer**

Shop It To Me, San Francisco, CA *January 2010–December 2011* 

As the sole designer, I designed new products, experiments, and various marketing collateral from web to print that impacted over 3 million users. Additionally, I started their user testing program. I conducted several user testing sessions. I worked closely with the CEO and Product Manager to take action from users' feedback. Besides user testing, I implemented a number of other design methods including developing personas, paper prototyping, wireframing, interactive brainstorming as well as creating several iterations of mockups in an agile environment.